question_data =  [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the play Oedipus Rex, Oedipus kills his father due to jealousy in loving his mother.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "St. Louis is the capital of the US State Missouri.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
